zymphonies.com 2019-11-12

# Privacy policy | Zymphonies

_Last updated: April 5, 2018_

By accessing the website at [http://www.zymphonies.com](http://www.zymphonies.com/), you are agreeing to be bound by these terms of service, Zymphonies Technologies (“Zymphonies,” “we” or “us”) respects the privacy of your information. We provide this explanation about our online information practices as a demonstration of our commitment to protect your privacy.

## Information collection and use

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. We will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.

## Your privileges

You have all privileges to stop receiving newsletter, marketing emails, RSS feeds or any other electronic communication. For this, you just need to click on “unsubscribe” button.

## Cookies

We use "cookies" to collect information. Cookies is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

## Security

We follow the high security principles to keep your personal information secured from getting misused or list and provide you the assurance to keep your information free of any risk.

## Third party practices

The Privacy Policy of an advertiser or promotional service appearing at our Site may differ from ours. We encourage you to read that policy before responding to the offer.

## Changes to our policy

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

## Contact us

If the information provided by you is incorrect or incomplete, then update it with us by sending an email. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
